They finally did it
Space defense system built to protect our world was accidentally triggered
And often follow Millions more died to survive with a curse
Disease chaos and violence became the leaders of the new world those with well
Usually landowners able to grow food formed new cities cities run by military
Bohemians pimps and sexual Outlaws open captioning
Innocence
We were forced into the hotch radioactive deserts created by the bombs
Colonies was found some of them peaceful happy and content
What is the radiation did its genetic damage most became violent
Fighting like Savages
Eventually feudal governments were formed
Longest bands of roving criminals using weapons and Machinery from the late 20th century
Spiritual group of genetically deformed Nomads trying to live in peace with what was left of all
Instead we will constantly running and hiding from these feudal Lords
Should my people the week in the old were brutally murdered.
The rest of our lives
Most of the hard labor we worked in that mine
Digging up minerals sold to the outside it was an outsider who came to us one day
An outsider who had no idea that he would change history and freedom UTSA
Bruce Banner
Paging Mr Kenner you have a phone
Hospitality Group
It's about time where the hell are you
Overlook Hotel at the border
Getting ready the kid wants to see the sights first you go in tomorrow morning Kenner
This job is higher risk the bishop uses criminals and outcasts of mine minerals we need
Those bastards are charging us whatever they want for the zirconium and that ain't good
The reports today in more border skirmishes with the rebel insurgents
An enemy ship probably no suicide missions to cross over the neutral zone
Defensive scramble immediately in membership outweigh Earth
The fierce battle one star Cruiser two battleships were destroyed
But it gets worse we lost another Colony on Mars
A rebel strike force of 10 ships landed on the planet is surrounded elliottville Smallville
Like Resort in the southern hemisphere Honeymooners
They're poorly armed and lack any military training my last contact reported
No survivors the loss of elliottville insurgents are now in control
90% of the Southern Hemisphere means they control all of the zirconium
You can see that your timing and your job are very important
You make the deals I take the meeting
Are you in junior getting along all right beautiful
Bossman
Got an interest in the future of Oblivion
He respects it
Don't look good Kenner
Reception
Take care of yourself the job it out
I want to keep you on my list nobody stays on top forever
Did you say something
One Day song
I'll be your love Saturday night
AMC Palace in Kenner
Is 54 a night can I meet you at 7 in the morning
Student housing
You can see Oblivion from here isn't it beautiful
Radioactive
I'm not stupid
Today's ozone reading is R22 for your protection
Do not expose yourself to the song for over 9 minutes
200 is required
I want to
What is this some kind of a joke I promise to take her
He wants to see Oblivion
Miss get out of the car
We'll get her out of the car the car
But nothing's been to Oblivion in the last hundred years
Please can I use your problem I don't lift a finger to help
This is Sheila
Wichita material man has something to do with this place
The mining operation
My father the boss man
First person to dig for zirconium on the ocean floor he building credible scientific
Laboratory in mine facility 300 miles below sea level
Green Life is Beautiful observation decks
Could watch the glow of zirconium gel sacks I remember it well
The best summer job I ever had
Take a mini-sub deep into the Draconian mind following the now-extinct albino Stingray
Nesting area once the bottom we could actually pass through the
Zirconium gel sacks unfortunately in about a month after I came
Topside was a massive earthquake
Open up a few scientists
The mini-subs just moments before the lab collapsed majority weren't so lucky
Buried alive the mines were also sealed probably forever
Oblivion
There's money in this garbage cheap Kenner if I readings become low enough
It's a beautiful day
Time to eat
How many times a year
United my beautiful fish
Go away you where did you get that fish you want a piece like that
Elijah get you one where you stink I'm not saying I'm going over the Border I can't get you
Dislike that if you going over that's the bishop country you get your own damn thing
Eliza
Going in going out Elijah nose
Organic
Mega slip around here
What is unhooked
Forget my medkit
That's good that's sealed
I'm going to find out where it came from to here
Kenner where you going
Is your child shut down
There's other movies around here
A pretty one
Vomiting popping
He's just what we're looking for
What's a rebound
Oh my God
1 bus
Call me Donny that's my name
You're going to be a long time
I found that it doesn't matter how rich potion you look on that
Xbox inside the cat
Kenner I got here yesterday
I came in from Overlook to measure radiation
What's a normal
Stitch braids beauty or you'll die
Welcome to the game
In Arena to the death
Mission 103
Mission 3
One kill anyone make me
No it's not her it's someone else
That's why we called the radio
Help me
Find it
Mr Turner
They call me the bishop I know what you're here for
Tom trying to do what you been ordered to do
And let me tell you
Your presence here is somewhat disturbing to business
We don't need that so now
Entertainment
Big bar
Turn on
Escape
Warning alert and now, there has been a long time
Escape escape to precaution
11 status is now in Colorado Springs
Country dancing
Need a lift
Chicken head
Paranormal
More less
New job
You don't have to do that
Where we going
What is my favorite
You shouldn't have
I already told you reading some atmosphere stuff
He's on the outside and once I work for need to find out if it's safe to come in here your LAN
The richest deposits of meconium left on Earth Juno zirconium is what we used
Pottery but now it has more important use recently in ship for my
Parallel universe entered our space sector they claim to come in peace but their purpose was
Clear the turn
Planets of our solar system into Stars
Dante Uranus using technology for advanced
Whoever they are stopped from Galaxy to Galaxy
Changing planets into burning Suns
Why we don't know
Our hunch is that there's some sort of markers probably
Star converter
Are our weapons were useless
Scientist with round-the-clock finally developing a new secret weapon
Quoniam bomb one of our Starcraft battlecruiser
Packman and bombs was launched from Earth it was in The Crew 2
Bravely and willing so they knew it was a one-way ticket
She fought her way through the air
Underneath the belly of a giant ship
That's why I'm here
Picture of our planet in our solar system depends on finding more zarconi
Are the pools of tried and failed why don't you go back to your world and your family before you regret it too
I don't have a family
My parents are dead they have been members of a mutant Rebel Force known as the resistance
Small set to believe in fighting violence with violence they were on
When my mother was suddenly captured by a kind of ballistic
Substances known as
Darkness ruling class nails
Father mutti races last usually for take me to pay jobs in
Listen to raising families
Days later my father upon realizing my mother's absence when searching for her
He found his way into the Whitey's domain
The rescue
Freedom look across the way but across physically wrong
Eventually they were captured and eaten alive
Yes but one day will destroy them all
Either way we wanted to be and we can help each other
We don't need some kind of help
Amanda
You know what the last
Life is going to send out the biggest party we've ever seen
Amen brother
What's the Colosseum
Hurry up little b**** his hunger grows
It's sold the first
I think it suits you
Please
Coliseum X time sometimes
Police about to die
Radioactive fallout was extreme it was able to reproduce usually gave birth to
Kind of sunburns
Lava spill twin modifications on unborn DNA were developed unfortunate
A terrorist attack destroyed a lab and killed
Hugfun
You are my children
It is time to listen to the voice inside your soul
Speed trigger Planet which was once beautiful and will
Again your ancestors spoke of the great white wolf
Good symbolize the strength and passion when the Wolves disappeared
The world crumbles
Spread like wildfire and go
Camping World in a flame men like the bishop
Rose to power his armies one smashing books for food
Precious Minerals
Our ancestors many sick from radiation
To the northern sector where they lived at one with nature but the bishop sooner
Get ready to job peaceful call me when you're just fluffy fight slave truck
He's been diminished Ox maybe if you fought bravely
Comebacks for his Superior Firepower
Roosevelt
Slave labor we have survived these dramas because we are
Because we know the job day of Freedom would have come a great
I will return and we will turn this Burning land into
Steven Lee
Reapplication to dry skin
It's the biggest I've ever seen
Find me to die. Going to be like a rat in the hole
Get out of my way
A better way I have an idea I'll climb
Are ducks on the Southside does anybody have a pocket knife
Hope raises its ugly head
No no no no no lies and news on the
This man
What's your name
You doing here I'll make a spear to kill snakes
Snakes
I've been misinformed cooking the whole
I've been down there tempting
For the outside that's me
What are you waiting for Armageddon
Nobody home
Get to the hospital
I said put across the border go get me a license Federal rehab
How you doing girl
Stay warm
Can you hear
Too loud
Real Racing
I need a drink
No problem
Turn 12 years old
That's for you
Radioactive
Kenner Kenner we have a prisoner up there what should we do with them
Do whatever you damn well please doing
Big rig
This man
My dear
First back but you have loss
The large storm clouds and change our policy game
How's your ancestors published great white wolf has returned
Name is Kenna
Neither one of you will be
His seed do this willingly with passion and gray
Gusto Free Yourself stations
Your Love Will fuel his heart and give him the strength
Flying to lead us to our Promised Land
Need for me now my children this is the last time
I will speak
Turn off
What do you want
Not once but twice
Better
Waiting for you everyone
Believing
Oh and got a beer or something
Ready where we going
What is No Beer
Back
You're in the lead I will follow you
Events that way okay
First time
Uncle Lazarus is dead
Very nice
Where you taking me
I told you that
We pay your people
Forget it
Okay
North Metro
Check-in hey where are you guys
Where are you
Anyone with the north Patrol
Still nothing from the North Pole
Sweetheart probably picked up some hot Beauty
Coliseum here
Bishop
Let me talk to sweetheart
Why the hell haven't you checked in
Good come see me when you get back your ex
God love you
Amen brother
Are you crazy
I don't know what the
Well I need a couple more parts
What does Minecraft
It's a funny feeling in my head
Can I set him down right there
Tell me pretty lies lies Eliza never lies Elijah
Have you been to the Coliseum
In-N-Out
Keep the people from I'm going in
Make you shine shoes and sweetheart
They didn't walk through the valley of The Shadow
They have something he's a scared of in the Coliseum
He calls it Santa's popper he's afraid of us
And they hurt him everything he said was
True Lies is the son of angels
Two again
Supreme
Boring every part beautiful woman she needs
Hey Kenneth going to fight tomorrow
How to get ready
Every move you make
You doing all this for the company for money reasons
Poverty violence food shortages
Shortly after the last Star Battle our president declared martial law
Their company is our armies were fighting in Space the government contracted a drive
Science Corporation to keep the peace
They were nothing but a simple robotic cyberpunks they became more and more
Eventually they took over the president quietly stepped aside but it's
Cabinet members weren't so lucky each was charged with treason mock trials were held in front of robe
Judges congressmen bureaucrats were tortured with red lasers and
Bid on National Television is epic proportions so
Things are so good
What about that woman
I'm different
Very beautiful
McKenna
North Patrol mission
Friday ratings
Remind me
Where are they
Cuban coming back
How do I look
Psychic parties in there
Welcome to the Colosseum Mr Tanner
You've livened things up magnificently for us all in Oblivion
And now Merry Christmas and goodbye
Got anything else
Overhear you
Bridget
Bang Bang
I heard Uncle Lazarus died
Pity you like the Coliseum it's its own
Course but it's comfortable Oblivion is a harsh land
It can twist the body and it can twist the soul
Which the soul tell us the secret he lie
Twisted Soul what are you talkin about my child
I know know you are one
Spaceship by
My whole life is a lie you don't like lies
You will see the truth now and it will be like seeing yourself
What's in a mirror place look
But you are
Dear mr. Preston enclosed you will find a copy of my report on the
Oblivion
Covered something in Oblivion I've discovered myself
A people whose courage and tenacity has helped me discover who I really am when I first
This Mission I was a shell of a man I am today now I have learned to trust the harmony which come
Listen to it heart a heart join with others beat stronger than any aliens
Remember Mr President
Rudolph candy
Grace
There is no need for Santa Barbara
Of course they are
What did you tell me where am I going to forget about mine
We're going to keep on buying a zirconium in the local resident
I don't belong.
Neither do I let's go home